One thing I'd like you to keep in mind is these people are not sadists, okay?
I'm not saying there's no sadists among them.
There's sadists in every single group.
But they don't believe that they're hurting the chickens.
They don't understand. They really don't.
They're conditioned from birth to believe that this is okay and that the chickens don't feel pain.
And if I'm in earshot of a little kid holding on to the mother's skirt and saying,
the chickens are crying, and I hear the mother say, they're not crying.
They're singing. They're happy to do this for you.
I tell the mother, no, they're not. They're suffering.
And I tell the little kid, you're right.
This hurts the chickens.
They're not singing. They're crying.
But it, you know, I mean, I think what we do is we try to plant seeds.
And that's why we give the chickens a little relief before they're swung.
And it's also good for the children to see that these are living creatures and that they need kindness.
That they need, you know, the Talmud actually says,
feed your chickens before you feed yourself.
These chickens never get fed.
They never get water.
Many of them die in the crates from dehydration, starvation, exposure to the elements, infection, sepsis.
I mean, it's really awful.
And many times they're injured because the crates are thrown so violently and dragged, their feet break off, their toes and their feet break off.
And we find, we find toes, you know, at these locations.
It's really, really awful.
And we, just so you know, we do not want anybody to rescue any chickens because we have a specific rescue team and we already have many, many.
So, so, so we can only rescue as many as we have homes and, you know, we're, we're beyond capacity right now.
The only chickens who we're going to actually rescue tonight are ones who are relinquished to us and we have our dead, Dr. Cleary here, who's going to be evaluating them and helping us to identify the ones that are, that, that need serious rescue.
And then we'll work with community affairs to try to negotiate them, um, to us.
So, does anybody have any questions?
Does anybody not want to be filmed at all?
Yeah, me.
I got you.
Okay.